and it was a program, you know, where there was
y era un programa ya se sabe donde se
yelling and that was normal. Now, I wouldn't
gritaba Y eso era lo normal ahora a m no
like to have a program like that. This
me gustaría tener un programa así esto
first thing she said is more than a
primero que ha dicho es más que una
clear reference to Sálvame when
Clara referencia a sálvame cuando
we're talking about a program where there was yelling
hablamos de un programa donde se gritaba
and so on, we're talking about a program, let's
y demás hablamos de un programa vamos a
say it clearly, vulgar, an
decirlo claro vulgar un programa
ordinary program, a program that seemed like you
ordinario un programa que parecía que
were in the neighborhood square and
estabas en la plazoleta del barrio y
seeing all the people there fighting and
viendo allí a toda la gente pelearse y
yelling and so on. There are many people who have had their
chillar y demás Hay mucha gente que le
character stolen, a lot of kico
han comido el personaje mucho kico her
Hernández Jorge Javier maybe too, and you
nández Jorge Javier quizás también y ya
no longer know who the character is or who
no sabes quién es el personaje ni quién
the person is and it's Uh you say, well,
es la persona y es Uh tú dices Bueno
come on, off camera you were trying to
venga tú fuera de cámaras intentabas
stop it, pay attention to this, what an
frenarlo atentos a esto que hecho
important fact, eh, of course, many times
importante eh claro muchas veces por
please no, aren't you ashamed to see her cry anymore,
favor no ya no te da pena verla llorar
please, this is eh, impressive, what she
por favor esto es eh impresionante lo
is implying here is that
que está dando aquí a entender es que
she asked the directors when they were
ella a los directores cuando le estaban
putting pressure on a character, a
apretando algún personaje algún
collaborator or whatever it was that was
colaborador o lo que sea que estaba
suffering, she would ask the directors,
sufriendo ella le pedía a los directores
now, now, and the directors would put more pressure on
ya ya y pero los directores apretaban